Guide to the Antiquarian bookseller catalog collection.
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- L
  - X346 L648, 1852 - 1858; unnumbered, nos. 86-149, 23 catalogs
    - W. S. Lincoln, Son; London (Box 988, Folder 6367)
  - X346 L648 I, 1855 - 1869; unnumbered, 8 catalogs
    - W. S. Lincoln, Son; London (Box 988, Folder 6368-6369)
  - X346 L69, 1872 - 1914; nos. 44-445, 138 catalogs
    Name variant: List & Francke
    - List Francke in Leipzig; Leipzig (Box 988, Folder 6370-6371)
    - List Francke in Leipzig; Leipzig (Box 989, Folder 6372-6378)
    - List Francke in Leipzig; Leipzig (Box 990, Folder 6379-6385)
    - List Francke in Leipzig; Leipzig (Box 991, Folder 6386-6391)
    - List Francke in Leipzig; Leipzig (Box 992, Folder 6392-6399)
  - X346 L7125, 1967 - 1969; nos. 1-10, 9 catalogs
    - Literary Heritage, Inc.; Sharon, Mass. (Box 993, Folder 6400-6403)
  - X346 L721, 1846 - 1857; unnumbered, 4 catalogs
    Name variant: Little, Brown & Co.
    - Charles C. Little and James Brown; Boston (Box 993, Folder 6404-6406)
    - Charles C. Little and James Brown; Boston (Box 994, Folder 6407)
  - X346 L721 I, undated; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - Little, Brown and Company; Boston, Mass. (Box 994, Folder 6408)
  - X346 L73, 1878 - 1914; nos. 1-80, 80 catalogs
    Number 1-40 in bound in 1 volume. Includes duplicates. Name variant: George Emery Littlefield
    - Geo. E. Littlefield; Boston, Mass. (Box 994, Folder 6409-6411)
    - Geo. E. Littlefield; Boston, Mass. (Box 995, Folder 6412)
  - X346 L7655, undated; nos. 4-8, 5 catalogs
    - Verena von Livonius; Stuttgart (Box 995, Folder 6413)
  - X346 L7675, 1957 - 1959; unnumbered, 7 supplements
    - Aux Amateurs de Livres; Paris (Box 995, Folder 6414)
  - X346 L826, 1929 - 1971; nos. 9-155, 67 catalogs
    - Librairie Edouard Lœwy; Paris (Box 995, Folder 6415-6418)
    - Librairie Edouard Lœwy; Paris (Box 996, Folder 6419-6424)
  - X346 L826 II, 1955; nos. 9-10, 2 catalogs
    - Librairie Edouard Lœwy; Paris (Box 996, Folder 6425)
  - X346 L8262, undated; nos. 57-90, 10 catalogs
    - Librairie Alexandre Loewy; Paris (Box 997, Folder 6426-6427)
  - X346 L837, 1929-1953, undated; nos. 30-100, 35 catalogs
    - Librairie M. Loliée; Paris (Box 997, Folder 6428-6432)
  - X346 L8544, undated; nos. 2-21, 18 catalogs
    - Long Island Book Center; Hempstead (Box 998, Folder 6433-6435)
  - X346 L861, 1814 - 1846; unnumbered, 12 catalogs
    - Longman, Hurst, Rees, Orme, Brown; London (Box 998, Folder 6436-8437)
    - Longman, Hurst, Rees, Orme, Brown; London (Box 999, Folder 8438-6441)
    - Longman, Hurst, Rees, Orme, Brown; London (Box 1000, Folder 6442-6446)
    - Longman, Hurst, Rees, Orme, Brown; London (Box 1001, Folder 6447)
  - X346 L87, undated; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Looker Evans; Essex (Box 1001, Folder 6448)
  - X346 L873, 1946 - 1970; nos. 1-60, 50 catalogs
    - Luis Bardon Lopez; Madrid (Box 1001, Folder 6449-6452)
    - Luis Bardon Lopez; Madrid (Box 1002, Folder 6453-6459)
    - Luis Bardon Lopez; Madrid (Box 1003, Folder 6460-6466)
  - X346 L9325, 1954-1957, undated; nos. 106-116, 9 lists
    - Gregory Lounz; New York, N. Y. (Box 1004, Folder 6467-6468)
  - X346 L945, 1933-1939, undated; nos. 1-144, 125 catalogs
    Name variant: David Low Booksellers Ltd.
    - David Low, Second-hand Bookseller; London (Box 1004, Folder 6469-6473)
    - David Low, Second-hand Bookseller; London (Box 1005, Folder 6474-6480)
    - David Low, Second-hand Bookseller; London (Box 1006, Folder 6481-6485)
  - X346 +L945, undated; no. 1, unnumbered, 2 lists
    - David Low Booksellers Ltd.; London (Box 1006, Folder 6486)
  - X346 L947, undated, 1933-1937, undated; nos. 1-165, 76 catalogs
    Name variant: Edward C. Lowe. Location variant: Gloucester, England
    - E. C. Lowe; Bath, England (Box 1006, Folder 6487-6489)
    - E. C. Lowe; Bath, England (Box 1007, Folder 6490-6495)
  - X346 L95, 1897 - 1971; nos. 5-1214, 480 catalogs
    - Lowe Brothers; Birmingham (Box 1008, Folder 6496-6501)
    - Lowe Brothers; Birmingham (Box 1009, Folder 6502-6506)
    - Lowe Brothers; Birmingham (Box 1010, Folder 6507-6512)
    - Lowe Brothers; Birmingham (Box 1011, Folder 6513-6518)
    - Lowe Brothers; Birmingham (Box 1012, Folder 6519-6525)
    - Lowe Brothers; Birmingham (Box 1013, Folder 6526-6531)
    - Lowe Brothers; Birmingham (Box 1014, Folder 6532-6537)
    - Lowe Brothers; Birmingham (Box 1015, Folder 6538-6540)
  - X346 L95 II, undated; nos. 83-93, 2 catalogs
    - Lowe Brothers; Birmingham (Box 1015, Folder 6541)
  - X346 L951, undated; nos. 3-13, 8 catalogs
    - James Lowe; New York, New York (Box 1015, Folder 6542)
  - X346 L958, 1920 - 1927; nos. 1-3, 3 catalogs
    - Luigi Lubrano; Napoli (Box 1015, Folder 6543)
  - X346 L958 II, 1908 - 1912; nos. 59-83, 7 catalogs
    - Luigi Lubrano; Napoli (Box 1016, Folder 6544-6545)
  - X346 L958 III, 1921 - 1931; nos. 1-50, 25 catalogs
    - Luigi Lubrano; Napoli (Box 1016, Folder 6546-6548)
  - X346 L959, 1962 - 1967; nos. 4-22, 7 catalogs
    - Philip Lozinski; Montreal, Canada (Box 1017, Folder 6549-6550)
  - X346 L97, 1890 - 1948; nos. 1-59, 45 catalogs
    - Luzac Co.; Great Russell Street, W.C. (Box 1017, Folder 6551-6555)
    - Luzac Co.; Great Russell Street, W.C. (Box 1018, Folder 6556-6560)
    - Luzac Co.; Great Russell Street, W.C. (Box 1019, Folder 6561-6564)
    - Luzac Co.; Great Russell Street, W.C. (Box 1020, Folder 6565-6568)
    - Luzac Co.; Great Russell Street, W.C. (Box 1021, Folder 6569-6571)
    - Luzac Co.; Great Russell Street, W.C. (Box 1022, Folder 6572-6576)
    - Luzac Co.; Great Russell Street, W.C. (Box 1023, Folder 6577-6580)
    - Luzac Co.; Great Russell Street, W.C. (Box 1024, Folder 6581-6584)
    - Luzac Co.; Great Russell Street, W.C. (Box 1025, Folder 6585-6587)
  - X346 L97 I, 1954 - 1967; nos. 55-74, 52 lists
    Title: Luzac's Oriental list and book review quarterly
    - Luzac; London (Box 1025, Folder 6588-6589)
    - Luzac; London (Box 1026, Folder 6590-6591)
  - X346 L97 II, 1943 - 1945; unnumbered, 5 catalogs
    - Luzac; London (Box 1026, Folder 6592)
  - X346 L972, 1938; nos. 1-120, 54 catalogs
    - Eric Lundberg; Walpole, New Hampshire (Box 1026, Folder 6593-6595)
    - Eric Lundberg; Walpole, New Hampshire (Box 1027, Folder 6596-6598)
  - X346 L9735, 1815; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - W. H. Lunn; London (Box 1027, Folder 6599)
  - X346 L993, 1902 - 1973; nos. 12-317, 161 catalogs
    - Herm. H. J. Lynge Son; Copenhagen (Box 1027, Folder 6600-6601)
    - Herm. H. J. Lynge Son; Copenhagen (Box 1028, Folder 6602-6606)
    - Herm. H. J. Lynge Son; Copenhagen (Box 1029, Folder 6607-6612)
    - Herm. H. J. Lynge Son; Copenhagen (Box 1030, Folder 6613-6618)
    - Herm. H. J. Lynge Son; Copenhagen (Box 1031, Folder 6619-6623)
    - Herm. H. J. Lynge Son; Copenhagen (Box 1032, Folder 6624-6628)
    - Herm. H. J. Lynge Son; Copenhagen (Box 1033, Folder 6629-6631)
  - X346 L993 I, 1950, undated; nos. 13-23, 9 catalogs
    - Herm H. J. Lynge Son; Copenhagen (Box 1033, Folder 6632)
- M
  - X346 M1, undated; nos. 10-49, 21 catalogs
    - M S Rare Books, Inc.; Weston, Massachusetts (Box 1034, Folder 6633-6638)
    - M S Rare Books, Inc.; Weston, Massachusetts (Box 1035, Folder 6639-6640)
  - X346 M11, 1947-1949, undated; nos. 5-45, 13 lists
    - W. A. Maas; North Wales (Box 1035, Folder 6641)
  - X346 M14 I, 1885 - 1931; nos. 33-447, 284 catalogs
    Numbers 92-107 bound, all others unbound. Name variant: Joseph McDonough Co.
    - Joseph McDonough; Albany, N. Y. (Box 1035, Folder 6642-6644)
    - Joseph McDonough; Albany, N. Y. (Box 1036, Folder 6645-6651)
    - Joseph McDonough; Albany, N. Y. (Box 1037, Folder 6652-6658)
    - Joseph McDonough; Albany, N. Y. (Box 1038, Folder 6659-6665)
    - Joseph McDonough; Albany, N. Y. (Box 1039, Folder 6666-6670)
  - X346 M149, undated; unnumbered, 4 lists
    - Ewen MacDuff; Shona, Mill Lane, Ashington, Sussex, England (Box 1039, Folder 6671)
  - X346 M169, undated; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Newman F. McGirr; Admore, Pa. (Box 1039, Folder 6672)
  - X346 M1691, undated; nos. 1-4, 4 catalogs
    - McGirr; Ardmore, Penna. (Box 1039, Folder 6673)
  - X346 M17 I, 1921-1922, undated; nos. 1-2, 3 catalogs
    - Martin A. McGoff; Liverpool, England (Box 1039, Folder 6674)
  - X346 M17 II, 1922 - 1940; nos. 2-46, 46 catalogs
    - Martin A. McGoff; Liverpool, England (Box 1039, Folder 6675)
    - Martin A. McGoff; Liverpool, England (Box 1040, Folder 6676-6682)
  - X346 M18, undated; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - R. J. Machen; San Francisco, Cal. (Box 1041, Folder 6683)
  - X346 M226, 1922 - 1957; nos. 1-166, 167 catalogs
    Name variant: McLeish & Sons
    - George Y. McLeish; London (Box 1041, Folder 6684-6690)
    - George Y. McLeish; London (Box 1042, Folder 6691-6696)
    - George Y. McLeish; London (Box 1043, Folder 6697-6703)
    - George Y. McLeish; London (Box 1044, Folder 6704-6709)
    - George Y. McLeish; London (Box 1045, Folder 6710-6716)
    - George Y. McLeish; London (Box 1046, Folder 6717-6722)
  - X346 M241, 1890 - 1933; nos. 17-191, 79 catalogs
    - Alexander W. Macphail; Edinburgh (Box 1047, Folder 6723-6729)
    - Alexander W. Macphail; Edinburgh (Box 1048, Folder 6730)
  - X346 M27, 1888 - 1985; nos. 80-1057, 656 catalogs
    Includes bound volumes
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1048, Folder 6731-6742)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1049, Folder 6743-6752)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1050, Folder 6753-6757)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1051, Folder 6758-6759)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1052, Folder 6760-6766)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1053, Folder 6767-6773)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1054, Folder 6774-6780)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1055, Folder 6781-6788)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1056, Folder 6789-6795)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1057, Folder 6796-6802)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1058, Folder 6803-6808)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1059, Folder 6809-6814)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1060, Folder 6815-6821)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1061, Folder 6822-6828)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1062, Folder 6829-6835)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1063, Folder 6836-6842)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1064, Folder 6843-6848)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1065, Folder 6849-6854)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1066, Folder 6855-6860)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1067, Folder 6861-6866)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1068, Folder 6867-6872)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1069, Folder 6873-6877)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1070, Folder 6878-6882)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1071, Folder 6883-6887)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1072, Folder 6888-6891)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1073, Folder 6892-6896)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1074, Folder 6897-6900)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1075, Folder 6901-6904)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1076, Folder 6905-6908)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1077, Folder 6909-6913)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1078, Folder 6914-6917)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1079, Folder 6918-6920)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1080, Folder 6921-6923)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1081, Folder 6924-6925)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1082, Folder 6926-6928)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1083, Folder 6929-6932)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1084, Folder 6933-6937)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1085, Folder 6938-6941)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1086, Folder 6942-6945)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1087, Folder 6946-6949)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1088, Folder 6950-6952)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1089, Folder 6953-6956)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1090, Folder 6957-6960)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1091, Folder 6961-6964)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1092, Folder 6965-6968)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1093, Folder 6969-6973)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1094, Folder 6974-6978)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1095, Folder 6979-6983)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1096, Folder 6984-6988)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1097, Folder 6989-6993)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1098, Folder 6994-6998)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1099, Folder 6999-7003)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1100, Folder 7004-7008)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1101, Folder 7009-7013)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1102, Folder 7014-7018)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1103, Folder 7019-7024)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1104, Folder 7025-7029)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1105, Folder 7030-7034)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1106, Folder 7035-7038)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1107, Folder 7039-7043)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1108, Folder 7044-7048)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1109, Folder 7049-7053)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1110, Folder 7054-7059)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1111, Folder 7060-7065)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1112, Folder 7066-7070)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1113, Folder 7071-7076)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1114, Folder 7077-7082)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1115, Folder 7083-7088)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1116, Folder 7089-7094)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1117, Folder 7095-7099)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1118, Folder 7100-7105)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1119, Folder 7106-7110)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1120, Folder 7111-7112)
  - X346 M27 II, undated, 1962, undated; nos. 1-5, 3 catalogs
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1120, Folder 7113-7114)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1121, Folder 7115)
  - X346 M27a, 1925 - 1936; unnumbered, 5 catalogs
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1121, Folder 7116-7117)
  - X346 M27m, 1939 - 1984; nos. 52-205, 46 catalogs
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1121, Folder 7118-7122)
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1122, Folder 7123-7125)
  - X346 M27n, 1934; nos. 1-2, 2 catalogs
    - Maggs Bros.; London (Box 1122, Folder 7126)
  - X346 M27p, 1933 - 1940; nos. 1-18, 16 catalogs
    - Maggs Bros.; Paris (Box 1122, Folder 7127-7129)
    - Maggs Bros.; Paris (Box 1123, Folder 7130-7132)
  - X346 M27pa, undated; nos. 1-2, unnumbered, 3 catalogs
    - Maggs Bros.; Paris (Box 1123, Folder 7133-1135)
  - X346 M276, 1912-1913, undated; nos. 12-25, 4 catalogs
    - Magrath Co.; Bradford (Box 1123, Folder 7136)
  - X346 M287, 1863 - 1935; unnumbered, 42 catalogs
    Name variants: J.Maisonneuve, Editeur; G.-P. Maisonneuve, Editeur
    - Maisonneuve et Cie,Libraires-Editeurs; Paris (Box 1124, Folder 7137-7141)
    - Maisonneuve et Cie,Libraires-Editeurs; Paris (Box 1125, Folder 7142-7145)
  - X346 M287 II, 1872 - 1883; nos. 1-9, 8 catalogs
    - Maisonneuve et Cie,Libraires-Editeurs; Paris (Box 1125, Folder 7146-7148)
  - X346 M287 III, 1890 - 1940; nos. 1-40, 11 catalogs
    - J. Maisonneuve, Editeur; Paris (Box 1126, Folder 7149-7150)
  - X346 M287 IV, 1913-1920, undated; nos. 1-23, 18 catalogs
    - Maisonneuve Freres, Editeurs; Paris (Box 1126, Folder 7151-7154)
  - X346 M287 V, undated; nos. 1-30, 18 catalogs
    - Gustave-Paul Maisonneuve, Succʳ; Paris (Box 1127, Folder 7155-7157)
  - X346 M287 VI, 1890 - 1891; nos. 1-3, 3 catalogs
    - J. Maisonneuve; Paris (Box 1127, Folder 7158)
  - X346 M287 VIII, 1952; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Adrien Maisonneuve; Paris (Box 1127, Folder 7159)
  - X346 M287 IX, undated, 1961-1968; nos. 20-31, 8 catalogs
    - G.-P. Maisonneuve-Max Besson, Succʳ; Paris (Box 1127, Folder 7160)
  - X346 M2885, 1818 - 1822; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - John Major; London (Box 1127, Folder 7161)
  - X346 M29, undated; nos. 1-13, 13 catalogs
    - Eric Malden; Suffolk, (Eng.) (Box 1128, Folder 7162-7163)
  - X346 M299, 1844; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - A. H. Maltby; New Haven, Conn. (Box 1128, Folder 7164)
  - X346 M31, 1948 - 1959; nos. 112-250, 39 catalogs
    - Libreria C. Mancuso; Palermo (Box 1128, Folder 7165-7167)
  - X346 M31 I, 1960 - 1964; nos. 1-50, 7 catalogs
    - C. Mancuso; Palermo (Box 1128, Folder 7168)
  - X346 M312, 1943; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - A. C. McClurg Co.; Chicago (Box 1128, Folder 7169)
  - X346 M316, 1928 - 1931; nos. 1-12, 8 catalogs
    - Librairie A. Manier; Paris, France (Box 1128, Folder 7170)
  - X346 M332, undated; unnumbered, nos. 28-48, 17 catalogs
    - F. Marcham; London (Box 1129, Folder 7171-7173)
  - X346 M332 I, 1948-1951; nos. 1-6, 6 catalogs
    - F. H. Marcham Co.; London (Box 1129, Folder 7174)
  - X346 M332 II, undated; nos. 1-8, 7 catalogs
    - F. Marcham; London (Box 1129, Folder 7175)
  - X346 M332 III, undated; nos. 1-8, 8 catalogs
    - F. Marcham; London (Box 1129, Folder 7176)
  - X346 M336, 1961-1966, undated; nos. 2-4, 3 catalogs
    - Yves Margotat; Paris (Box 1129, Folder 7177)
  - X346 M337, 1919 - 1971; nos. 37-293, 163 catalogs
    Name variant: Ancienne Maison Margraff
    - Alph. Margraff; Paris (Box 1129, Folder 7178)
    - Alph. Margraff; Paris (Box 1130, Folder 7179-7184)
    - Alph. Margraff; Paris (Box 1131, Folder 7185-7193)
    - Alph. Margraff; Paris (Box 1132, Folder 7194-7200)
    - Alph. Margraff; Paris (Box 1133, Folder 7201-7202)
  - X346 M344, 1922-1951, undated; nos. 1-56, 56 catalogs
    - Marks Co.; London (Box 1133, Folder 7203-7207)
    - Marks Co.; London (Box 1134, Folder 7208-7213)
  - X346 M345 I, undated; nos. 6-118, 105 catalogs
    Name variants: Marlborough Rare Books Ltd.; Marlborough Rare Books
    - Marlborough Rare Books Limited; London (Box 1135, Folder 7214-7219)
    - Marlborough Rare Books Limited; London (Box 1136, Folder 7220-7226)
    - Marlborough Rare Books Limited; London (Box 1137, Folder 7227-7233)
    - Marlborough Rare Books Limited; London (Box 1138, Folder 7234-7239)
    - Marlborough Rare Books Limited; London (Box 1139, Folder 7240-7245)
  - X346 M345 II, 1948; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Marlborough Rare Books Limited; London (Box 1139, Folder 7246)
  - X346 M345 III, undated, 1985-1986; unnumbered, .35 catalogs
    - Marlborough Rare Books Ltd.; London (Box 1140, Folder 7247-7252)
    - Marlborough Rare Books Ltd.; London (Box 1141, Folder 7253-7255)
  - X346 M3455, undated; nos. 1-10, 10 catalogs
    - Marlyn Books; Detroit, Michigan (Box 1141, Folder 7256-7258)
    - Marlyn Books; Detroit, Michigan (Box 1142, Folder 7259)
  - X346 M3522, 1757; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Charles Marsh, Bookseller; [London] (Box 1142, Folder 7260)
  - X346 M363, 1946 - 1959; unnumbered, 8 catalogs
    - Libreria Marti; La Habana, Cuba (Box 1142, Folder 7261-7262)
  - X346 M369, 1888; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Alchemy, Magic, Talismans, etc.; London (Box 1142, Folder 7263)
  - X346 M381, 1957 - 1958; nos. 3-6, 3 catalogs
    - Masque Bookshop; London (Box 1142, Folder 7264)
  - X346 M421, 1942 - 1968; nos. 16-72, 50 catalogs
    Location variant: Poole (Dorset), England
    - Alister Mathews; Swanage (Dorset), England (Box 1142, Folder 7265-7266)
    - Alister Mathews; Swanage (Dorset), England (Box 1143, Folder 7267-7271)
  - X346 M422 II, 1922-1958, undated; nos. 1-188, 190 catalogs
    Name variant: Elkin Mathews Ltd. Location variants: Hertfordshire; Takeley Bishops Stortford
    - Elkin Mathews Limited; London (Box 1143, Folder 7272-7274)
    - Elkin Mathews Limited; London (Box 1144, Folder 7275-7280)
    - Elkin Mathews Limited; London (Box 1145, Folder 7281-7286)
    - Elkin Mathews Limited; London (Box 1146, Folder 7287-7293)
    - Elkin Mathews Limited; London (Box 1147, Folder 7294-7299)
    - Elkin Mathews Limited; London (Box 1148, Folder 7300-7305)
    - Elkin Mathews Limited; London (Box 1149, Folder 7306-7312)
    - Elkin Mathews Limited; London (Box 1150, Folder 7313-7318)
  - X346 M424, 1908 - 1909; nos. 1-7, 4 catalogs
    - Librairie G. Mathias; Paris (Box 1151, Folder 7319)
  - X346 M425, 1847 - 1849; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - De L. Mathias (Augustin); Paris (Box 1151, Folder 7320)
  - X346 M446, 1859; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - James E. Mauran; New York (Box 1151, Folder 7321)
  - x346 M447 I, 1894; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - A. Maurice Co.; London (Box 1151, Folder 7322)
  - X346 M447 II, undated; nos. 88- 249, 63 catalogs
    - A. Maurice Co.; London (Box 1151, Folder 7323-7327)
    - A. Maurice Co.; London (Box 1152, Folder 7328)
  - X346 M449, 1913 - 1914; nos. 57-61a, 5 catalogs
    - Mawson Swan Morgan Ltd.; Newcastle-on Tyne (Box 1152, Folder 7329)
  - X346 M453, undated, 1886-1893, undated; nos. 82-346, 105 catalogs
    Name variant: Buchhandlung Mayer & Müller
    - Mayer Müller; Berlin (Box 1152, Folder 7330-7334)
    - Mayer Müller; Berlin (Box 1153, Folder 7335-7340)
    - Mayer Müller; Berlin (Box 1154, Folder 7341-7346)
    - Mayer Müller; Berlin (Box 1155, Folder 7347)
  - X346 M453 I, undated; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Mayer Müller G. M. B. H.; Leipzig (Box 1155, Folder 7348)
  - X346 M472, undated; nos. 1-64, 11 catalogs
    - B. J. F. Meehan; Bath, England (Box 1155, Folder 7349-7350)
  - X346 M546, undated; nos. 71-159, 22 catalogs
    - Rudolf Merkel; Erlangen (Box 1155, Folder 7351-7354)
    - Rudolf Merkel; Erlangen (Box 1156, Folder 7355)
  - X346 M548, undated; nos. 126-205, 66 catalogs
    Name & location variant: Kurt B. Merlander; Burbank, California
    - Dr. Kurt Merlander; Los Angeles, California (Box 1156, Folder 7356-7361)
    - Dr. Kurt Merlander; Los Angeles, California (Box 1157, Folder 7362)
  - X346 M55, 1948 - 1962; nos. 1-44, 31 catalogs
    - Edgar P. Merrett, Academic Book Service; New York, N. Y. (Box 1157, Folder 7263-7367)
  - X346 M553, 1973; no. 17, 1 list
    - Merrion Book Co.; London, England (Box 1158, Folder 7368)
  - X346 M564, 1951; no. 2, 1 catalog
    - Jose M. Mestrea; Barcelona (Box 1158, Folder 7369)
  - X346 M578, 1913-1936, undated; nos. 9-45, 24 catalogs
    - Jules Meynial Succ'; Paris (Box 1158, Folder 7370-7373)
  - X346 M578 II, 1905 - 1948; nos. 45-107, 26 catalogs
    Name variant: Andrė Meynial; Paris
    - Jules Meynial; Paris (Box 1158, Folder 7374-7377)
    - Jules Meynial; Paris (Box 1159, Folder 7378-7582)
  - X346 M578 IV, 1946 - 1952; nos. 46-53, 7 catalogs
    - Claude et Jean Meynial; Paris (Box 1159, Folder 7383)
  - X346 M5812, undated; nos. 7-45, 5 catalogs
    - Michael Ginsberg Books, Inc.; Sharon, Mass. (Box 1159, Folder 7384)
    - Michael Ginsberg Books, Inc.; Sharon, Mass. (Box 1160, Folder 7385)
  - X346 M582, undated; unnumbered, nos. 3-40, 23 catalogs
    - G. Michelmore Co.; London (Box 1160, Folder 7386-7389)
    - G. Michelmore Co.; London (Box 1161, Folder 7390-7395)
  - X346 M582 I, undated, 1923; unnumbered, 7 catalogs
    - G. Michelmore Co.; London (Box 1162, Folder 7396-7400)
  - X346 M585, undated; nos. 57-101, 37 catalogs
    - Midland Rare Book Company; Mansfield, Ohio (Box 1163, Folder 7401-7407)
    - Midland Rare Book Company; Mansfield, Ohio (Box 1164, Folder 7408-7413)
  - X346 M6117, 1852 - 1858; nos. 33-43, 2 catalogs
    - Thomas Millard; London (Box 1164, Folder 7414)
  - X346 M6117 II, 1853 - 1872; nos. 1-62, 5 catalogs
    - Thomas Millard's Book-Store; London (Box 1164, Folder 7415)
  - X346 M6148, 1838 - 1840; nos. 3-8, 2 catalogs
    - Miller's Catalogue of Books, Ancient and Modern; London (Box 1165, Folder 7416)
  - X346 M6157, undated, 1852; nos. 1-45, 4 catalogs
    - William Miller; London (Box 1165, Folder 7417)
  - X346 M6195, 1924; no. 5, 1 catalog
    - Miller and Beyer; New York, N. Y. (Box 1165, Folder 7418)
  - X346 M64, 1953 - 1970; nos. 5-17:1, 9 catalogs
    - S. Millman; Brooklyn, New York (Box 1165, Folder 7419-7420)
  - X346 M665, undated; nos. 15-73, 22 catalogs
    - George Robert Minkoff Inc. Rare Books; Great Barrington, Mass. (Box 1165, Folder 7421-7424)
  - X346 M6684, undated, 1986; unnumbered, nos. 2-79, 38 catalogs
    Name variant: Arthur H. Minters
    - Arthur H. Minters; Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 1166, Folder 7425-7430)
    - Arthur H. Minters; Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 1167, Folder 7431-7434)
  - X346 M734, 1914 - 1956; unnumbered, 23 catalogs
    Name variant: Gabriel Molina (Sucesora)
    - Gabriel Molina Sucesor de Viuda de Rico; Madrid (Box 1167, Folder 7435-7437)